<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reproducible Research on STAT-5014 Fall 2020</title>
    <link>http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/tags/reproducible-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reproducible Research on STAT-5014 Fall 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/tags/reproducible-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 2 - Data structures, Reproducible Research, loading, cleaning and munging data in R</title>
      <link>http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/2020/08/22/lecture-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/2020/08/22/lecture-2/</guid>
      <description>Today’s Agenda  Review the concepts of Reproducible Research
 Review Git
 Importing, cleaning and munging data Summarizing and exploring data Vectors, matrices, and data frames   Reproducible Research | Review This was the scenario:
You had worked 6 months to analyze a data set. Someone else analyzes the data and comes to different conclusions. How good are your notes???
Answer: Awesome, because you annotated your code with text to create a RR compendium</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 1 - Introductions, Reproducible Research, (a little) R, and (a little) Git</title>
      <link>http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/2020/08/20/lecture-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/2020/08/20/lecture-1/</guid>
      <description>Today’s Agenda  Introduce the course Introduce the concepts of Reproducible Research Introduce Git
 Introduce R as the (main) platform for the course Homework 1   Course Learning Objectives  R programming Reproducible research concepts Good programming practices
 Data cleaning and munging Git fundamentals Markdown Python basics SAS basics   Tentative Course Lecture Schedule Due dates are solid, however, feel free to race ahead.
https://rsettlage.github.io/STAT_5014_Fall_2020/schedule/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>